I don’t want this, I want a colorful guest circle, I want a colorful guest circle. There is no colorful guest circle,
I won't eat. Son, daddy will find you a colorful guest circle. That funny gentleman over there,
Do you know what a colorful guest circle is? Where else can I get it?
Are you talking about the rare Big Red colorful guest circle in the new event Treasure Month? It seems so.
If you want to get it, I suggest you buy the No. 8 Dam Treasure Map.
Treasure point No. 8 has a higher probability of being red. I have exactly ten treasure maps of No. 8 here.
A 10 million Harvard coin.
Do you want it? I bought all the new ones. Treasure spot No. 8 is next to the pipe in the corner of the container area on the north side. Got it,
It's not that boss. Could it be that he lied to me? How did you open this treasure spot No. 8? All pocket watches.
Good brother, why are you here? By the way, do you have colorful engraved circles? I don’t have the colorful engraved small circles,
But I have a small engraving circle, which should be about the same, since they are all engraving small circles anyway. Then give me this first,
Next time I will take you to the space base. OK, take it first. Xiao Pu Zai, I got you a small circle.
Look! What I want is a colorful guest circle, colorful! Don’t call me on the road again, do you understand?
Who is that person? Irrelevant.